How has the skills that you learned from being
a salesman translated and helped you own a company
of your own at such a young age? The thing
is, is that when you're in sales, you can't Google
experience. You can't Google it. You have to go
through it. And someone can teach you all the
tricks, all the cool things to say. You
could dress perfect, but until you've been told no,
until you've been cussed out, until you've been
screamed at, until you have people tell you no
after no after no, and you still have to
have that same attitude and still be able to deliver
the message the right way, you won't get
it. There's no textbook that can teach it besides
making thousands and thousands of cold calls,
knocking on doors, going through so many different
experiences. And when you're in sales and you
learn how to communicate to all different types
of people, different ethnicities, different
backgrounds, different ages, different experiences,
you have no choice but to get better.